Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 568, Folder 8)
  - Item 29: Dear Members of 101st Congress and Friends of APWU, 1989; Publication (Box 568, Folder 8)
    Author: Patrick J. Nilan; Roy Braunstein; Moe Biller
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 569, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Joint Bargaining Committee Bulletin, 1981; Publication (Box 569, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.1 (1981:Apr. 13)
  - Item 2: Joint Bargaining Committee Bulletin, 1981; Publication (Box 569, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.2 (1981:Apr. 16)
  - Item 3: Joint Bargaining Committee Bulletin, 1981; Publication (Box 569, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.2 (1981:May 1)
  - Item 4: Joint Bargaining Committee Bulletin, 1981; Publication (Box 569, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.4 (1981:May 28
  - Item 5: Joint Bargaining Committee Bulletin, 1981; Publication (Box 569, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.6 (1981:June 12)
  - Item 6: Joint Bargaining Committee Bulletin, 1984; Publication (Box 569, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.1 (1984:May 23)
  - Item 7: Joint Bargaining Committee Bulletin, 1987; Publication (Box 569, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.6 (1987:July 10)
  - Item 8: Joint Bargaining Committee Bulletin, 1990; Publication (Box 569, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.90-1 (1990:Aug. 30)
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 569, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: NAPS Letter, 1979; Publication (Box 569, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.31:no.14-17, 19-21, 23-25 (1979)
  - Item 2: NAPS Letter, 1980; Publication (Box 569, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.1-3, 5-9, 12, 16-24 (1980)
  - Item 3: NAPS Letter, 1981; Publication (Box 569, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.1, 3-7, 9-18, 20-23, 25-27 (1981)
  - Item 4: NAPS Letter, 1982; Publication (Box 569, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.34:no.1-9, 11-24 (1982)
  - Item 5: NAPS Letter, 1983; Publication (Box 569, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.1-19, 20- 26 (1983)
  - Item 6: NAPS Letter, 1984; Publication (Box 569, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.1- 6, 8, 13, 14-18, 20-24 (1984)
  - Item 7: NAPS Letter, 1985; Publication (Box 569, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.37:no.2-26 (1985)
  - Item 8: NAPS Letter, 1986; Publication (Box 569, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.1-8, 10-13 (1986)
  - Item 9: NAPS Letter, 1988; Publication (Box 569, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.40:no.17-19 (1988)
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 569, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: NAPS Letter, 1977; Publication (Box 569, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.14-16, 19-22, 25 (1977)
  - Item 2: NAPS Letter, 1978; Publication (Box 569, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.1, 3-9, 11-26 (1978)
  - Item 3: NAPS Letter, 1979; Publication (Box 569, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.1-13 22 (1979)
  - Item 4: NAPS Letter, 1980; Publication (Box 569, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.4, 11, 15 (1980)
  - Item 5: NAPS Letter, 1986; Publication (Box 569, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.14-18, 20-24 (1986)
  - Item 6: NAPS Letter, 1987; Publication (Box 569, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.39:no.1-11, 13-25 (1987)
  - Item 7: NAPS Letter, 1988; Publication (Box 569, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.40:no.1-16, 20-25 (1988)
  - Item 8: NAPS Letter, 1989; Publication (Box 569, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.41:no.1-26 (1989)
  - Item 9: NAPS Letter, 1990; Publication (Box 569, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.42:no.1-13 (1990)
  - Item 10: National Alliance Reporter, 1978; Publication (Box 569, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.3 (1978:July 13)
  - Item 11: National Alliance Reporter, 1978; Publication (Box 569, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.4 (1978:Oct. 23)
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 569, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: NAPS Letter, 1985-1996 (Box 569, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.37:no.1 (1985)
  - Item 2: NAPS Letter, 1985-1996 (Box 569, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.42:no.14- 16, 18-20 (1990)
  - Item 3: NAPS Letter, 1985-1996 (Box 569, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.43:no.2-26 (1991)
  - Item 4: NAPS Letter, 1985-1996 (Box 569, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.44:no.1-16, 18-29 (1992)
  - Item 5: NAPS Letter, 1985-1996 (Box 569, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.45:no.1-3, 15, 26 (1993)
  - Item 6: NAPS Letter, 1985-1996 (Box 569, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.46:no.1-23 (1994)
  - Item 7: NAPS Letter, 1985-1996 (Box 569, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.47:no.1-26 (1995)
  - Item 8: NAPS Letter, 1985-1996 (Box 569, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.48:no.1-13 (1996)
  - Item 9: NAPS Letter, 1994; Publication (Box 569, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.5 (1994:Aug. 12)
- National Education Association, Publication (Box 569, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A strong America needs strong public schools, 1984; Publication (Box 569, Folder 5)
    Author: National Education Association
    Notes: Folder of information about Walter Mondale
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 569, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Master Agreement - for the 1975-1976 season (Box 569, Folder 6)
    Author: Rochester Philharmonic Orchestra
  - Item 2: Immediate Release - Victor Fuentealba becomes President of the American Federation of Musicians, 1978; Publication (Box 569, Folder 6)
    Author: American Federation of Musicians
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 570, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, 1990; Publication (Box 570, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Constitution and By-Laws, 1992; Publication (Box 570, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Constitution and By-Laws, 1992; Publication (Box 570, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Questions & Answers about the APWU, Publication (Box 570, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: 1990 Resolutions to be acted upon by the National Convention, Publication (Box 570, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: APWU 10th Biennial convention, 1990, Publication (Box 570, Folder 1)
    Notes: Program
  - Item 7: bibliography additions, 1992-1993 (Box 570, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 1992.
  - Item 8: bibliography additions, 1992-1993 (Box 570, Folder 1)
    Notes: October 1993.
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: American Postal Workers Union News Service, 1987; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.5 (1987:Mar. 20)
  - Item 2: American Postal Workers Union News Service, 1990; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.11 (1990:July 10)
  - Item 3: Welcome to the fold: meet your union., 1979; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: American Postal Workers Union News Service: Convention Bulletin, 1986; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.1-5 (1986:Aug. 11-15)
  - Item 5: Postal Worker Alert, 1987; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1987)
  - Item 6: Postal Worker Alert, Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.1
  - Item 7: Elect our friends - do it with COPA in '88! - Defeat our enemies!, 1988; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Voting Analysis of the 100th Congress, 1988; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Letters to the Editor, 1988; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Reagan OMB to USPS - Drop DEAD!, 1988; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: HR4150 USPS "Off-Budget" & COPA "88 Campaign, 1988; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Questions & Answers about the APWU, Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: American Postal Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Library Information Center, Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: American Postal Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Library Information Center, Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Benefits at a glance, 1987; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Benefits at a glance, 1987; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: American Postal Workers Union News Service, 1985; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.21 (1985:Aug. 2)
  - Item 18: American Postal Workers Union News Service, 1988; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.18:no.10 (1988:Apr. 29)
  - Item 19: Regarding the numerous inquiries from the field as to what action can be taken as to whether or not American Postal, 1981; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
    Author: Moe Biller
  - Item 20: On Sept. 19, 1981, the AFL-CIO will hold an event in Washington, DC, Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Constitution Committee Report to the 10th biennial National Convention of the., 1990; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Salt City Post, 1989; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
    Notes: May 1989.
  - Item 23: Salt City Post, 1989; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
    Notes: June 1989.
  - Item 24: APWU 1989 Legislative goals - October 6 (Target Date) Congressional Adjournment Goal!!, Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: A Textbook for Postal Stewards, 1980; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: Hear President Moe Biller on 'The Larry King Show', 1988; Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
    Notes: May 17, 1988.
  - Item 27: Here are some guidelines to make your letter perfect, Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: Voter Registration Form, Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 29: APWU Gets Non-Members Reinstated to Level 5!, Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Item 30: If Seeing Is Believing, Publication (Box 570, Folder 2)
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 570, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution Committee Report to the 11th Biennial National Convention, 1992; Publication (Box 570, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Constitution Committee Report to the 11th Biennial National Convention, 1992; Publication (Box 570, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Constitution Committee Report to the 12th Biennial National Convention, 1994; Publication (Box 570, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: 1978 Resolutions to be acted upon by the National Convention, Publication (Box 570, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: 1978 Resolutions to be acted upon by the National Convention, Publication (Box 570, Folder 3)
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 570, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Directory of the US Senate and the US House of Representatives, 1981-1982 (Box 570, Folder 4)
    Notes: 97th Congress
  - Item 2: Directory of the US Senate and the US House of Representatives, 1983-1984 (Box 570, Folder 4)
    Notes: 98th Congress
  - Item 3: Directory of the US Senate and the US House of Representatives, 1985-1986 (Box 570, Folder 4)
    Notes: 99th Congress
  - Item 4: Directory of the US Senate and the US House of Representatives, 1986-1987 (Box 570, Folder 4)
    Notes: 100th Congress
  - Item 5: 6th Biennial National Convention, 1982; Publication (Box 570, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Post Office women for equal rights equal powers, Publication (Box 570, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: APWU steward's handbook: a guide for the APWU's frontline leadership, Publication (Box 570, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: APWU steward's handbook: a guide for the APWU's frontline leadership, Publication (Box 570, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: The APWU Team Offers Coverage For Your Family Needs, Publication (Box 570, Folder 4)
    Notes: Poster
  - Item 10: Vote to Ratify Tentative Agreement, Publication (Box 570, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Postal Action Day, June 25, Publication (Box 570, Folder 4)
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 571, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Alcoholism is treatable, 1979; Publication (Box 571, Folder 1)
    Notes: Publication no.108
  - Item 2: Alcoholism is treatable, 1979; Publication (Box 571, Folder 1)
    Notes: Publication no.108. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Post Office women for equal rights equals power, Publication (Box 571, Folder 1)
- National League of Postmasters, Publication (Box 571, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Charter and Code of Governing Rules of the National League of Postmasters of the United States: Officers Manual: Code of Governing Rules of the National Postmasters Auxiliary and the Retired League Postmasters, 1988; Publication (Box 571, Folder 2)
    Author: National League of Postmasters
  - Item 2: Charter and Code of Governing Rules of the National League of Postmasters of the United States: Officers Manual: Code of Governing Rules of the National Postmasters Auxiliary and the Retired League Postmasters, 1985; Publication (Box 571, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Charter and Code of Governing Rules of the National League of Postmasters of the United States: Code of Governing Rules of the National Postmasters Auxiliary and the Retired League Postmasters, 1993; Publication (Box 571, Folder 2)
- National League of Postmasters, Publication (Box 571, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Postmasters Advocate Express, 1988; Publication (Box 571, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1988:Apr. 1)
  - Item 2: News Release - 'Enclosed find copy of letter from Sen. Jennings Randolph to Pres. Jennings. The letter itself is self-explanatory. The mark-up session is now scheduled for June 9 and 10, 1976', Publication (Box 571, Folder 3)
    Author: Eugene B. Dalton
  - Item 3: The Empire Express, 1990; Publication (Box 571, Folder 3)
    Notes: Sep./Oct. 1990
- National Probation Officers' Association (U.S.), Publication (Box 571, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Constitution -- (Probation Dept., City of New York), Publication (Box 571, Folder 4)
    Author: National Probation Officers' Association (U.S.)
- PEF (New York State Public Employees Federation), AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 571, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the State of New York and the Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO, 1985-1988 (Box 571, Folder 5)
    Author: PEF (New York State Public Employees Federation), AFL-CIO
    Notes: Professional, Scientific and Technical Services Unit
  - Item 2: Agreement between the State of New York and the Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO, 1988-1991 (Box 571, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Agreement between the State of New York and the Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO, 1979-1982 (Box 571, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the State of New York and the Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO, 1982-1985 (Box 571, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Memorandum of agreement between the Executive Branch of the State of New York and the Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO, 1991-1995 (Box 571, Folder 5)
- PEF (New York State Public Employees Federation), AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 571, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Memorandum of agreement between the Executive Branch of the State of New York and the Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO, 1985-1988 (Box 571, Folder 6)
- PEF (New York State Public Employees Federation), AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: PEF 15th Annual Convention - Program, 1993; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: PAC Legislative Report, 1986; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
    Notes: October 1986.
  - Item 3: PAC Legislative Report, 1988; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1988:Oct.)
  - Item 4: Believe it or not!, 1992; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1992:Apr.)
  - Item 5: Memo: Convention Information - 8th Annual Convention - 1986, Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
    Author: Maggie Litzenberger
  - Item 6: Convention '86 is fast approaching, 1986; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
    Author: Rand Condell; James Sheedy
  - Item 7: Official list of Delegates - 8th Annual Convention, 1986; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Memo: Per capita dues dispute with AFT/NYSUT, 1986; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
    Author: Rand Condell
  - Item 9: Labor/management notes--Quarterly Labor/Management Report.., 1986; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Constitution and bylaws, 1986; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: 1986 Legislative Report, Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: PEF Convention Program, 1986; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Convention Resolutions, 1986; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Ned Regan: Man or Myth?, 1986; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Important member survey for 1991 contract issues, Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Labor-management manual - 7th Annual Convention, 1985; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Folder of misc. information sheets, Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Dear Region 8 PEF Members, 1986; Publication (Box 571, Folder 7)